datam.com 2014-03-29

# Datam

This Privacy Policy describes how FNBox Ventures Inc. (FNBox) collect, use and share personal information of users of the website www.datam.com (the Site), which is owned by FNBox, and any services available through the Site. FNBox is committed to protecting the confidentiality of your personal information. We use state of the art hardware and encryption procedures to safeguard the privacy of your information.

Please read the following to learn more about what information we may collect form our users and how such information is used and shared. By visiting our Site you are accepting the practices outlined in this Privacy Policy of our Site. If you do not agree with this terms, please do not visit or use this Site.

We are committed to protecting the confidentiality of your personal information.

## What information we collect form our users and how we use it

Through the registration in our Site, we may collect personal information such as name,‎ email address,‎ phone number, and any other type of personal information users submit during the course of normal correspondence with FNBox. We may use your email address to send you special offers, in response to users-initiated inquiries, to provide services requested by the users, to alert of changes in our services or features, and to provide users with requested information about our services. You may unsubscribe from these at any time, in accordance with section 3. 

We use the information we collect from our users as follows:

  1. a) **To provide our services.** FNBox uses the information we collect from users to help them process their orders, track transactions, issue the invoices, offer new services, answer users comments and questions, send technical notifications or update of the services. When a user purchase our services, we will transfer its personal information to the applicable advertiser with whom we cooperate.
  2. b) **To send communications from the Site.** FNBox will occasionally send users information or messages on new services, promotions and other service-related announcements we consider relevant for the users.
  3. c) **For Marketing purposes.** FNBox may share users personal information with affiliated companies, for use in their ad serving and marketing programs, and with service providers who assist us with our marketing efforts.
  4. d) **Dispute resolution.** FNBox may make disclosures of information from users in order to comply with the law and when we believe in good faith that the release of that information is necessary to investigate fraud, an intellectual property infringement, or other unlawful activity that may result in liability for FNBox or its users.

## Collection and Use of Information

If you no longer wish to be a part of our users database or you no longer wish to receive communications to your email, you may contact us to team@datam.com, or in the case of emails, you may also opt-out of receiving them by following the instructions included in each newsletter or communication.

## Disclosure of users information

FNBox will never sell, rent, lease or disclose your information to any third parties in ways other than disclosed in this privacy policy.

Notwithstanding the above, the user acknowledges that FNBox may transfer all or part of the users information to any of its subsidiaries and/or affiliates at any time and in whatever format it deems appropriate.

In the event we go through a business transition, such as a merger, acquisition by another company, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, your information will likely be among the assets transferred. You will be notified via email and/or prominent notice on our Site for 30 days of any such change in ownership or control of your information.

## Security mesures

At FNBox security is important. FNBox employs appropriate measures, including advanced technology, to protect information collected against unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration or destruction. These measures may include, among others, encryption procedures, physical access security and other appropriate technologies. FNBox continually reviews and enhances its security systems, as necessary. Vostu stores information about its users on servers, where only employees who need information to perform a specific job are granted access to it. 

Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet or any wireless network can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect data, you accept that there are security and privacy limitations of the Internet which are beyond our control and that the security, integrity and privacy of any and all information and data exchanged between you and us through the Site cannot be guaranteed. Furthermore, we are not responsible for any third party which may view or tampered with the information in transit. 

## Legal capacity of users

Only those who, in accordance with the laws in force in their place of residence, can validly give their consent to enter into contracts may access and use the services offered by FNBox. Those who, in accordance with the laws in force, do not have such legal capacity may only use the Site through their legal representative, who shall remain liable for all the acts performed on behalf of the incompetent.

Whenever the lack of capacity is due to age, such lack may not be cured. Access to the Site by a minor is strictly prohibited, unless the laws of the place in which the minor resides provide otherwise. In this case, liability arising from services to which minors have access, shall be imposed on the adults responsible for them. Therefore, minors who access the Site shall obtain their parents', guardians', or legal representatives' permission, whenever such access is permitted by law.

As regards legal persons' representatives, Users shall have sufficient authority to act on behalf of the represented entity and to bind it to the terms hereof. If the User lacks such sufficient authority, or acts beyond the authorized scope, he/she shall be deemed to be bound personally.

## Information from other sources

### Cookies

The user acknowledges that FNBox uses cookies for tracking transaction, identification, security, to analyze trends, administer the Site and improve and customize the experience for the users. A cookie is a small text file that is stored on a user's computer for record-keeping purposes. We use cookies on this Site. We do not collect personally identifiable information with the cookies, we use them to show the websites the users visited before ours and the time spent in them. Furthermore, the cookies allow us track the number of register users in the Site and the activity of the user. We do not link the information we store in cookies to any personally identifiable information you submit while on our Site.

You can remove cookies by following directions provided in your Internet browser's "help" file. If you reject cookies, you may still use our Site. Third parties may use cookies on this Site, which allow them to recognize a user's cookie when a user visits this site. The information that they collect and share through this technology is not personally identifiable. FNBox does not control the use of cookies by third parties. 

### Log Files

As is true of most sites, we gather certain information automatically and store it in log files. This information includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, operating system, date/time stamp, the uniform resource locator (URL) of the sites you visited before visiting our Site and time spent in them, and the use you made of our Site.

We use this information, which does not identify individual users, to analyze trends, to administer the site, to track users' movements around the Site and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. We do not link this automatically-collected data to personally identifiable information. 

## Third Party websites The Site may be linked to or from other websites

The privacy and security practices of websites linked to or from the Site are not covered by this Privacy Policy, and FNBox is not responsible for the content or privacy practices employed by them. Neither does FNBox control or warrant the utility, merchantability or workmanship of the products or services offered at third-party websites. If you visit other websites please make sure to review their privacy policy and security practices. 

## Changes to this Privacy Policy

If FNBox decides to change this Privacy Policy, we will post those changes on our homepage so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. 

We reserve the right to modify this privacy policy at any time, so please review it frequently.
